securedsearch.org 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy

Our data protection practices in connection with the products and services provided by us and certain third parties (the “Products and Services”) are described in this privacy policy. Please make sure that you also read the Products and Services’ End User License Agreement, which, together with this privacy policy, govern your use of the Products and Services.

Please note that the Products and Services include also products and services by Bytefence, Google, Microsoft and Yahoo. Your download, installation and use of the Products and Services indicates that you also consent to Bytefence’s, Google’s, Microsoft’s and Yahoo’s privacy policies which can be found at the following links: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>, [http://go.Microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=248686](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=248686), [https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/search/details.html and http://bytefence.com/privacy.aspx](https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/search/details.html%20and%20http://bytefence.com/privacy.aspx). Please also note that none of Google, Microsoft and Yahoo are our affiliates.

Your download, installation and use of the Products and Services and/or your acceptance of this privacy policy and/or End User License Agreement indicates that you consent to the data collection, retention and usage practices set forth herein.

  1. Collection and Use of Information

    1. Information We Collect

We may collect the following information: IP address, browser(s) type and details about the operating system installed on your device. We collect and use such information in order to operate the Products and Services, analyze their performance and to improve them.

    2. Information Provided by You

We will store records of communications we had with you when you contact us, which may include your email address and other personal information included in such communication, in order to support your use of the Products and Services, and, if we deem necessary, look into any issues you may raise.

    3. Tracking Mechanisms

In order to enable us to collect the information specified above, the Products and Services may utilize tracking technologies such as cookies and/or other technologies. A cookie is a small text file saved on your computer to help store preferences and other information that is used on webpages that you visit. We may use cookies to better understand how you interact with the Software and to customize and improve the Software. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can change the settings of your browser at any time to delete/disable cookies. However, some features of the Software may not function properly if you disable cookies.

  2. How We Share and Disclose Information

    1. Sharing and Disclosure of Information

We may share and/or disclose your personal and non-personal information only to the extent permitted by this privacy policy and applicable law, including without limitation for the following purposes: (i) compliance with applicable laws, rules and/or regulations, other legal obligations or procedures, or to protect our rights; (ii) enforcement of this privacy policy and/or End User License Agreement; and/or (iii) ensure enforcement against illegal activities by third parties. You hereby acknowledges and consent to the transfer, share, sell and disclosure of your information in connection with a liquidation event, sale of our assets, merger, acquisition or reorganization.

    2. Third Party Services Providers

We utilize Amazon Web Software, Inc. servers for storage of personal information of all our users. Please review the following document by Amazon regarding protection of your personal information: <https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/>.

    3. Other Company Divisions and Affiliates

We may share your information with other divisions of our company, parent companies, subsidiaries and sister companies (“Affiliates”), in order to allow us to operate and improve the Products and Services, and our Affiliates’ products and services, and for that purpose we may combine your information collected by us with information collected by our Affiliates.

    4. Data Transfer

In the event that you are a European resident, you hereby acknowledge and consent to the transfer of information we collect from you outside of the European Economic Area for the purpose of processing it.

  3. Security

We are utilizing reasonable security safeguards for the protection of your personal information. However, in light of the nature of the online environment, we are not able to fully ensure the security of any information that we collect or receive. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee that information stored on our servers will not be accessed by unauthorized persons.

  4. Updating and Deleting Personal Information

You may send us a request to update or delete your personal information stored in our servers at the following email address: [support@bytefence.com](mailto:support@bytefence.com). Your request will be processed and handled within 30 days.

  5. Children

The Products and Services are not intended and/or directed to children below the age of 13. In the event that we have actual knowledge that a child below the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will take the necessary steps required by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Please contact us if your child provided us with personal information at [support@bytefence.com](mailto:support@bytefence.com).

  6. Changes and Updates

In the event of any material changes to this privacy policy, we will display a notice through the Products and Services and/or other means.

  7. Contact

Please contact us with any questions at support@bytefence.com.
